(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-29T23:44:04.493187",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ご来場のみなさまへ
Attention For Visitors
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The concert will be starting soon.
WAH! Good Morning, Afternoon, and Evening! It's me, Ina!
I hope everyone is excited for the concert! I know I am!
I've been AmiAmi's ambassador for a full year now,
and it's been so much fun sharing all the great memories and the cool merch with you!
I've been using AmiAmi for a long time, but I still get excited every time I spot something WAHnderful on AmiAmi
— it's like finding treasure!
Whenever you find cute merch of your oshi on AmiAmi, be sure to let us know, okay?
Let's give AmiAmi a big thank you for everything they've done this year!
Everyone say, Thank you AmiAmi!
Anyways, Let's make more amazing memories tonight!
Make sure to cheer with everything you've got, okay?
WAH!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
hololive English 3rd Concert ALL FOR ONE
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one.
Let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
Yuh!
Rise up!
Coming closer now!
Bring it on!
Get down
Right now!
Fighters!
Fearless!
Step it up, step it up now!
We've got the power, unstoppable
The fire burning up inside our soul
Nothing brings us down
No matter what, we're gonna break through
Never stop, gotta keep it going on and on we go
Crashing into the dark
Yeah, we gon' break the rules
Nobody can do what we can, no!
Get up and move!
Break all of the rules, now move into the groove
Keep it extra cool
We're extraordinary, got 'em all under control
Ayo, back it up, break it down, let us guide the way...
Louder, louder to the beat!
Fly higher, higher to the sky!
Hey now, we gon' vibe
Ain't no time to waste
Yes, listen to your heart then you'll find your way
Got lost inside reality
I heard a whisper
Calling me
I see it now, we've found ourselves
That's who we are...
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Start again
We're never gonna stop!
光り輝く stars
Glowing stars,
導き合ってダンス
guiding each other, we dance.
Hey, start again
Let go and let it flow!
Ready or not, here we go!
Supernatural,
煌めく sparkling
glittering, sparkling!
無限に広がる stage
On an infinitely expanding stage,
響かせて, now sing along!
resonate it, now sing along!
Feel the rhythm taking over, keep it going on and on!
Shout out loud and reach out to the moon
Not afraid, there's nothing left to lose!
A start of something more
Yes! Turn it up!
Into the new world
We are unbreakable now!
Hey now, what's goin' on?
Let's take it real slow from head to toe
So ready or not, level up to our heat
Burning, burning, burning!
Focus, all eyes on me!
Step by step, funk it out!
Push it to the limit till the end, yeah, yeah!
Got lost inside reality
I heard a whisper
Calling me
I see it now, we've found ourselves
That's who we are...
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Start again
We're never gonna stop!
光り輝く stars
Glowing stars,
導き合ってダンス
guiding each other, we dance.
Hey, start again
Let go and let it flow!
Ready or not, here we go!
Supernatural revenge!
Break it down!
Holla back, woah!
Can't nobody get in the way of us no more
Lights, camera, action, revolutionary!
Ayo, come on! Get up, get up!
Never gonna lose, we're invincible now
Going higher and higher, the energy grows!
Got it all under control, here we go!
On another level, keep it up, we're comin' out!
Lala, louder
Go lala, louder
Go lala, louder now!
This is us, we rulin' the world!
Start again
We're never gonna stop!
光り輝く stars
Glowing stars,
導き合ってダンス
guiding each other, we dance.
Hey, start again
Let go and let it flow!
Ready or not, here we go!
Supernatural,
煌めく sparkling
glittering, sparkling!
無限に広がる stage
On an infinitely expanding stage,
響かせて, now sing along!
resonate it, now sing along!
Feel the rhythm taking over, keep it going on and on!
Shout out loud and reach out to the moon
Not afraid, there's nothing left to lose!
A start of something more
Yes! Turn it up!
Into the new world
We are unbreakable!
We are unbreakable now!
私のもの そう私のもの
Mine, yes, it's all mine!
千の黄金
A thousand pieces of gold,
数百年の財宝 この船に眠る
hundreds of years of treasure lie sleeping in this ship.
古びた伝説は 呪われた幽霊船に
An ancient legend tells of a cursed ghost ship
続く夜の潮路
sailing endlessly through the night currents.
Ah, ready?
Are you ready to rock?
Rocking!
蠢く蛇電 閃光は
Wriggling ball lightning, a flash...
呪われた幽霊船に
on the cursed ghost ship...
続く夜の潮路
sailing endlessly through the night currents.
そこに痛みが残る
Where pain still lingers,
太古のヒビが入る
ancient cracks begin to form,
のらりくらり...
drifting aimlessly along...
だから知らないでしょう
So you probably don't know, do you?
無謀な賭けを 若き盗賊よ
making a reckless gamble, young thief,
命妄想で 後悔に伏させてやる
I'll make you bow in regret with your life delusion,
止まない雨の弾丸で
with a relentless rain of bullets.
鬱陶しいほど この身に焦がれる
Annoyingly enough, you long for this body,
宿命の炎が 眩む色彩 晒す
as the flames of fate expose dazzling colors.
宝石なのかな
If it is a gemstone...
私のもの
It's mine.
そう わたしのもの
Yes, it's mine.
歌ってみろ 命の証を
Try singing out the proof of your life,
あなたのもと
by your side,
求めるすべてを
everything you seek,
輝かせ
make it shine.
濡れてみせて
Show me you're drenched,
誰の手も 握り掴むなら
if you're going to hold anyone's hand,
歌声とともに 沈め
sink along with the singing voice.
今宵もまた 勝利を飾れる
Tonight again, adorned with victory,
極小の海賊の秘宝を
over the tiny pirate's treasure,
高笑う
laughing out loud.
まやかしの金銀財宝
Deceptive gold and silver treasures,
飾るのみの 刃の玉座
a throne of blades meant only for display,
宝飾の星ども
stars of jewels...
命取りの魅力を狙う
Aiming for deadly allure,
愚者にお仕置きだす
punishing the foolish ones.
浅ましい野心家を
Capturing wretched opportunists
捕らえるこの生贄の場で
at this place of sacrifice,
影の底で忍び寄る 絶望の渦丸めて
rolling up the vortex of despair creeping at the bottom of darkness,
歌の閉じた箱
a closed box of song.
ためらっちゃいな 諦めちゃいな
Hesitate, give up,
罠になっても逃げられるのに
even though you could escape if it turned into a trap,
まだにしがみついてる
you're still clinging on.
欲望が重いから
Because your desires are heavy.
私のもの
It's mine,
そう わたしのもの
yes, it's mine,
自分自身を信じ込ませた
I made myself believe it.
スポットライト
Spotlight,
縛り付けて
binding me tight,
だって気付いた
because I realized
呪いの手口 この世の怪奇
the curse's method, the strangeness of this world.
目を覚まして
Wake up,
あなたの悪心から
taking away the suffocating feeling
連れ出す息苦しさを
born from your evil heart,
蹴散らして
kick it away.
わたしのもの
It's mine,
まだ わたしのもの
still mine,
勝者の誇り 抱き締めさせて
let me hold the victor's pride,
割れない魂までも
even an unbreakable soul.
悩む憂鬱 永遠の響きを
Troubled melancholy, an eternal resonance,
どんな幻惑と戦っていたでしょう
what kind of illusion was I fighting against?
だけど決意は砕けない
But my resolve won't shatter,
哀歌
an elegy,
予定に抗い向けて
facing against the destined plan...
曰くを宿した船
A ship bearing legends,
今は残っていくだけ
now just leaving behind,
神はもう居ないから
because God is no longer here.
Hello New York!
Are you ready to put your hands up?
I wanna see all your hands!
I want to see all your hands!
And let's go!
Put your hands up!
Put your, put your hands up!
行きにも帰りにもなく ぐるぐる
Going neither back nor forth, round and round,
手に持つ食糧イズ ズーチー
food in hand is cheese.
メシは食わねば ねるねるねるね
Gotta eat food, Nerunerunerune,
タイムスリップ
time slip!
や! ここどこ?! どこどこ?!
Ya! Where is this?! Where, where?!
ダンシング ダーウィン 斬新 進行
Dancing Darwin, innovative progress,
感謝あり 人類発祥地
full of gratitude, birthplace of humanity!
いい感じ! 早々出発進行!
Feeling good! Departing right away!
去る者追わざる パッパッピッピッポー!
Don't chase those who leave, pa-pa-pi-pi-poo!
Put your hands up!
Put your, put your hands up!
我等もほら これで大人
Look, now we are adults too!
ワン! ワン! ワンワンワン! ワン!
Woof! Woof! Woof woof woof! Woof!
脳内全開
Full throttle inside the brain,
やっぱポッポで
after all, super hyped up,
回らない目でおろおろでは アイアイ
flustered with eyes spinning around, aye aye!
あの日開けた
The door that was opened on that day
ドアってのは
is...
じゃい じゃい じゃい じゃい PARTY
Jai jai jai jai party
O-W-A-A-I-I 気分ハイ 言葉
O-W-A-A-I-I feeling high, words
O-W-A-A-I-I 愛のマイ 言葉
O-W-A-A-I-I, my words of love
つながってんだかどうなんだ 人生目処だね 眠いっす
Are we connected or what? Life's set, I'm sleepy
思い描いている 猿 人 ガール
The ape, human, girl I'm picturing
推しいんだ 働いてんだ 錬金なんだ
I'm a fan, working hard, it's alchemy
休みの前日に気が気... 昨日のアー
On the day before a day off, I can't settle...
ランチタイム 淡々と進行 人類滅亡
Lunchtime, smoothly proceeding, human extinction
あるでしょ AI 暴走
It happens, right? AI running amok
あ、もう斬新... そうそう警鐘鳴らそう
Ah, so novel... Yeah yeah, let's sound the alarm
もう指指まで 1, 2, 3 オンライン オンライン タンタンシャー
Down to my fingers 1, 2, 3 online online...
Okay New York, you're gonna hate me for saying this...
Let's go vintage!
愛のネタバレ「別れ」っぽいな
Spoiler for love: "breakup"-ish
人生のネタバレ「死ぬ」っぽいな
Spoiler for life: "death"-ish
ほら言え ほら言え
Come on, say it, come on, say it
Everyone, we're just getting started, so give me your energy!
Put your hands up! Put your hands up!
別に摩訶不思議
Not particularly profound
これだろう？「だな」
This is it, right? "I guess"
そう 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1!
Yeah, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1!
エラー！
Error!
到来 限界へ
Reaching the absolute limit
やっぱ ポッポッパーティー
After all, pop pop party
破らず舞い踊れ
Dance without breaking
感動しないで どうやって生まれたの？ ほら 飛ばせ
Don't be moved, how was it born? Look, blast off!
じゃい じゃい じゃい じゃい PARTY
Jai jai jai jai party
O-W-A-A-I-I 気分ハイ 言葉
O-W-A-A-I-I feeling high, words
O-W-A-A-I-I 愛のマイ 言葉
O-W-A-A-I-I, my words of love
Put your hands up! Put your hands up!
New York!
Are you ready for some spice?
Oh, ah, lalala, na-na-na-na-na-na
Oh no, fell into the abyss unknown
Left me bleeding, heartless, all alone, oh, oh
No control, oh, oh
Don't you dare apologize
Turn my back and felt a cold knife
Listen up, 'cause here's some advice
You're out of time, way out of line
It's taking over like a renegade
Eye for an eye, I'll make you cry
Tearing it down, do just what I wanna
Keep calling me a sinner (Know you think so)
Chimera (Got me twisted)
Chimera (Such a misfit)
Taking the crown, now you're calling me king
You gonna hear 'em all sing (Now sing it)
Chimera (Louder like that)
Chimera (Make 'em all 'ah')
Don't back it up, don't back it up, keep that aim
I got thoughts that will drive you insane
Come over if you like, we'll have a lot of fun
But I got a lot of bite
I do what I want, make sure you don't forget it
An army on my back, say I'm sick, I'm just sadistic
Not living in a lie, pariah in the light
I wanna see the way you bleed
It's taking over like a renegade
Eye for an eye, I'll make you cry
Tearing it down, do just what I wanna
Keep calling me a sinner (Know you think so)
Chimera (Got me twisted)
Chimera (Such a misfit)
Taking the crown, now you're calling me king
You gonna hear 'em all sing (Now sing it)
Chimera (Louder like that)
Chimera (Make 'em all 'ah')
I want it all, so gimme some more
Flames burnt me up, down into my core
Oh, you wished I'd stay down, but then I just rise
You're not my enemy, baby, you're dead to me
Hear my voice that's screaming out loud, no doubt, yeah!
Yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!
La-la-la-la-la-la
No, YOU!
Tearing it down to just what I want, ah
Keep calling me a sinner
Yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!
Taking the crown, now you're calling me king
And you're gonna hear them all sing
Now sing it!
Yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!
La-la-la-la-la-la
Oh no, no one's cheating! Calli!
What? You're cheating on Calli?
Yeah, didn't you know?
Oh, yeah...
Oh, Yabe! Yabe!
We're not doing anything wrong!
No, no, we were just hugging as friends!
It was just tete! Tete!
Yes.
Kiwawa! IRyS!
Okay, let's introduce ourselves, yeah?
Hi!
Yes, you!
Starting with the cheater... Oh no.
The cheater?!
No, I'm not a cheater!
Okay, go ahead! Kiwawa!
I wish I was someone else right now...
...but I'm Takanashi Kiara from hololive English -Myth-! Yay!
And you?
Hi! It's IRyS from hololive English -Promise-!
Can I get a HiRyS?
HiRyS!
Let's go!
Thank you!
We just performed a really hyped performance...
Yes.
...of CHIMERA!
This is not my first time performing with you on your song.
Yeah, they put us together a lot these days.
Yeah, it's kind of a trend.
It is.
KiRyS is trending!
KiRyS is the trend! Yeah!
I'm sure they can't get enough of us, right?
No, of course they can't!
That's why we're here now, too.
We're spice.
Yeah.
We're sexy.
Oh, yes we are!
Yes we are!
Well, you know, it's the first time seeing...
That's right.
...which means...
Oh!
...we're gonna do the sad news, right?
Yes.
But I want to deliver the sad news!
It's our first time, so I want to do it too!
Well, I want to do it!
Well, in that case, we battle it out!
We're battling it out? In front of all these people?
Yeah, there's no problem. They're gonna cheer for us.
Yeah.
Well, when you think of battles, what do you think of?
I think like, recently, a lot of the EN members have been doing arm wrestling.
And I'm very well-known for being a noodle-arm person. What about you?
I am very strong!
Oh!
Everyone knows that IRyS is very strong.
Yeah, you are.
Well, I usually am left-handed, but I will use my right hand to give you a chance.
Okay?
Thank you, Senpai!
Okay, okay, okay!
I will take that chance right now!
Let's go!
Okay, come here! Come here!
Okay.
Count us down!
Three, two, one, go!
I'm gonna win! I'm gonna win!
Yes!
I defeated her!
With her non-dominant arm!
Yeah, that was my right hand, though! My left hand is my dominant arm, so that wasn't completely fair.
Oh!
Let's do another game!
Another game?
Yes!
I mean, yeah, that's true. It wasn't fair. In that case, what do you have in mind?
There's this game called Blue Light, Red Light... Not Blue Light!
Red Light, Green Light!
Okay.
Okay, then you perhaps stand on that side...
...and I'll go towards you.
Okay.
All right, all right.
Gotcha.
Okay, then I...
I can win this!
I will get you, okay?
No, no, no!
Okay.
Red light!
Green light!
Oh, sorry, I...
We're starting, we're starting!
Okay, okay.
Red light!
Green light!
Red light! Green light!
Red light! Green light! Red light!
Not my butt!
Okay, yay!
But that means it's a draw.
A draw?
Which means...
We get to say it together?
Te-te ending!
It's not like this was scripted or anything. I swear I actually...
The only thing that was scripted was our entrance.
Oh, yeah... That.
Okay, then! Let's do it! Let's do this. Okay.
Everybody watching on YouTube...
Are you aware that if you don't have a ticket, you might be not able to watch any more of this?
Are you aware that if you don't have a ticket, you might not be able to watch any more of this?
What?!
Yes, guys! This is the last of the free part on YouTube!
If you want to watch more, you have to buy the streaming tickets!
Available in the description, on the official website!
Probably down there, yeah. You can go get a streaming ticket!
Yeah, you would be crying like me until you buy them! Yes!
Do what she says, I recommend it.
As long as you buy them, you'll be happy and you'll be able to watch the rest of the concert!
Yes, yes, yes! They're saying it too!
Buy it! Buy it!
Besides that, one more thing...
Now that you got your tickets and you're ready to take even more screenshots...
Make sure to share them and your thoughts on social media using the hashtag #holoAllForOne! Yes!
So, speaking of All For One, I think it's time for us to...
You know, say the thing.
Yeah, the thing! You guys are all aware by now, right? Because of yesterday.
It's called "All For One", we say it together.
We say it together, yeah. All of us.
Are you in, or what? Okay!
All for one. All for one.
Okay. Ready? Okay. 3, 2, 1...
All For One!
Ooh...
Just look around and see—it's so incredible!
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment, I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together, reaching out from far and wide
And suddenly, you're here by my side!
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one.
Let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
Everything's in motion
Get up and start the celebration
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see (uh-huh)
Feel the love and the energy!
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're here together, finally!
Every moment takes my breath away
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song
And suddenly, our hearts beat as one!
Every voice ringing loud and clear, so glad to be here
Together, we're all for one.
Let's sing! All for one!
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
Keep up the hype, it's good times, good vibes
Remember this night the rest of our lives
Hey!
Raise up your hands and sway, your light will lead our way
We're shining, all for one!
All for one!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended! Thank you for watching!